Good Friday morning,
President Trump now eyeing a new push for peace.
This time between Russia and Ukraine.
It's October 17th.
This is Today.
High stakes,
President Trump set to host Ukraine's
leader at the White House just one day after
a surprise phone call with Russia's Vladimir Putin.
Trump now saying a second summit with him is in the works.
We want to get peace.
We want to stop the killing.
This morning,
the new hope bolstered by the ceasefire
in the Middle East that an end to
Russia's war could also be within reach.
A live report from the White House.
Breaking
news,
former national security adviser John Bolton
surrendering to authorities this morning
after being indicted,
now facing 18 counts of mishandling classified information.
Bolton
denying wrongdoing and saying he's just the
latest target of a weaponized Justice Department.
Will have the very latest emergency evacuations,
military planes being used to airlift people
from remote villages in Alaska,
decimated by a catastrophic storm.
So traumatic folks are coming in
here with just clothes on their back.
In some cases,
we'll take you inside the dramatic rescues
as one of the largest operations of its kind
plays out this morning on the rise.
Robo calls and spam texts now soaring to a six year high.
I literally get about 30 calls a day this morning.
The growing annoyance felt by millions all across the country.
The new ways that scammers are getting through and what you should
never do when you receive them to protect your private information.
Guitar hero.
Trivies pouring in for Kiss Legend,
Ace Fraley,
who helped revolutionize rock with his trademark
style and makeup will celebrate his life and legacy.
All that plus look out.
Eye injuries on the rise as the popularity of pickleball soars.
Straight ahead,
what you need to know before taking the court.
And battle of the ages.
A wild Thursday night duel between the Steelers and Bengals featuring
quarterbacks in their 40's Cincinnati pulling off a huge
upset in the final seconds.
Snap good, hold good, kick good.
The highlights from the game being called the icy
hot bowl to kick off another big week in the NFL.
Today, Friday, October 17th, 2025.
From NBC News,
this is Today with Savannah Guthrie and Greg Melvin.
From Studio 1A in Rockefeller Plaza.
Good morning and welcome to today on this Friday morning,
glad you're with us.
I'm Chanel Jones alongside Willie Geisen for
Savannah and Craig this morning.
You know, I'm watching that
football game last night Chanel watching 40 years old and 41
year old quarterbacks go at it thinking I still have a few good
years left.
I have to put on the old high school football pads
and get out there.
What a great game.
The old guy showing they
can still do it.
We're rooting for them.
We'll have more on
that coming up in just a bit.
But first, we want to get to the
major developments happening today on several stories.
NBC
News has learned former national security
adviser and Trump critic John Bolton has
surrendered to authorities this morning
after being accused of mishandling
classified information.
We're also watching the White House where later
today President Trump will meet with
Ukraine's President Vladimir Zelensky
just hours after he announced another
summit with Russia's Vladimir Putin over
the war in Ukraine.
There has also been a major shakeup at the Pentagon.
The
Admiral overseeing those strikes on
alleged drug boats near Venezuela now
saying he is retiring after just one year on the job.
We have it all covered starting with NBC's
chief White House correspondent Peter Alexander.
Peter, good morning.
Chanel.
Good morning.
President Trump says great progress was
made in that call with Vladimir Putin.
Of course,
time is going to test that their meeting will take place in Budapest,
Hungary.
The president says no date set,
but just days after President Trump secured that
historic but fragile ceasefire in the Middle East.
President Zelensky now says that he
hopes that deal will provide new momentum
for a possible end to the fighting with Russia.
President Trump this morning preparing for
another high stakes summit with Vladimir Putin.
The announcement coming after what the president
says was a productive two hour call on Thursday
with Russia's president as President Trump
tries to broker a deal to end Russia's three year old war in Ukraine.
We want to get peace.
We want to stop the killing.
The call setting the table for Ukrainian President Vladimir
Zelensky's White House visit today.
Today,
Ukraine's presence expected to urge President
Trump to allow the transfer of long
range Tomahawk missiles to Ukraine.
But President Trump remains
noncommittal.
They're very accurate.
They're very good, but we need them too.
So I don't
know what we can do about that.
Putin fiercely opposes any possible transfer,
which a top
Russian aid warned would significantly damage U.S.
Russian relations.
The upcoming meeting
comes more than two months after
President Trump welcomed Putin to Alaska,
a summit that
produced no major progress and fueled President
Trump's public frustration with Putin.
I'm very disappointed because Vladimir
and I had a very good relationship,
probably still
do.
In the weeks since, Russia has only increased
its strikes against Ukraine.
The president hopes to use his personal relationship
with Putin to end the war there while he ramps
up pressure in another region of his foreign
policy.
We have a lot of drugs coming in from Venezuela.
Overnight, NBC News confirms that
the military carried out another strike
against an alleged Venezuelan drug boat.
But for the
first time,
there were survivors,
according to a U.S.
official.
It's the latest of multiple
strikes in international waters aimed,
the president says,
at stopping the drug trade
from Venezuela.
But it comes as the head of U.S.
Southern Command, which
oversees the
strikes,
unexpectedly announced he would retire
yesterday without giving any reason.
The
strikes have drawn criticism from lawmakers.
But President Trump has doubled down,
revealing there's been covert CIA action
within Venezuela and even implying the U.S.
military could get involved on the ground.
We are certainly looking at land now because
we've got the sea very well under control.
And Peter, you mentioned we're learning the
military is ramping up its presence even more near Venezuela.
What can you tell us?
Yeah, Chanel, you're right.
Flight tracker data reviewed by NBC News shows just two days ago.
But this week,
two B-52 bombers took off from a Louisiana
air base and flew for several hours
off the Venezuelan coast.
Obviously,
this is a major show of force in what is an already
volatile region.
B-52s can carry dozens of precision guided bombs.
They have previously
been used by the U.S.
military in places like Iraq and Afghanistan to inflict significant
damage on targets there.
Chanel.
All right, Peter, thank you.
Also, this morning we are
following new developments in the indictment of John Bolton,
a one-time Trump aide turned
adversary,
the former national security adviser accused
of mishandling classified information.
His case,
the third in as many weeks brought against a prominent Trump critic.
NBC's senior
legal correspondent Laura Jarrett is here with more.
Laura, good morning.
Willie, good morning to you.
John Bolton, not just any Trump critic.
He's been a stalwart
of Republican politics for decades now,
but his highly public break with the president
reaching a new level now with this indictment,
as he's expected in court today.
He once held
the nation's top secrets,
but this morning John Bolton surrendering to authorities seen
entering the courthouse, any comment
now facing 18 counts of mishandling classified information.
The former national security adviser turned
outspoken Trump critic indicted by a federal
grand jury Thursday accused of sharing sensitive
information he learned in the early years of
the first Trump administration with two relatives,
providing them with diary-like entries of his
day-to-day activities.
Prosecutors say Bolton sent more than 1,000 pages of meticulous notes
over private AOL and Gmail accounts to his
family members he referred to as his editors
before he started shopping a memoir,
which offered a devastating portrait of Trump's
leadership.
The indictment alleging at least one of
Bolton's email accounts was later hacked
by someone associated with the Iranian government,
but he failed to tell the FBI the sensitive
information that was allegedly compromised.
The president, who said in the past Bolton
should go to jail, reacting to the indictment.
I think he's,
you know, a bad person.
I think
he's a bad guy.
Yeah.
Bolton has faced scrutiny for his handling of classified information
since the waning days of Trump's first term,
but he maintains the book contains no classified
information and the Biden administration
ended the probe with no charges.
But armed with a
search warrant in August,
the FBI searched his home and his office,
carrying out several
boxes and seizing his devices.
He's already come after me and several others.
I think
it is a retribution presidency.
Bolton now vowing to fight these charges,
casting himself
as the latest target of Trump weaponizing the justice department,
likening the second
Trump administration to Joseph Stalin.
It all follows the indictments of two other Trump
foes in recent weeks,
but those charges brought by a single political appointee,
whereas the
far more detailed indictment of Bolton bearing
the names of multiple career prosecutors.
So Laura, as you
as you allude to there in the piece,
this indictment of John Bolton is
different than the indictment of
Saint James Comey.
Yeah, one of
these is not like the other.
This is not about a full day
mortgage application or lying to
Congress.
This is about highly
classified materials, which he
knowingly apparently distributed
to his family members, according
to prosecutors.
He's gonna have a
tough road to fight this.
He
says he did nothing wrong, but
you see prosecutors already
building their case using his own
public media statements against
him, showing he should have known better guys.
Keep a close eye on this one, Laura.
Thank
you.
Let's bring in Kristen Welker,
moderator of Meet the Press.
Kristen, good morning to
you.
Hi, Chanel.
Good morning to you.
Great to be with you.
Let's talk about this for
a moment.
Just how politically significant is
this indictment and could we expect to
see more?
Great question.
Look,
this is hugely significant because this is the third Trump
rival who's now been indicted in recent weeks.
As Laura just pointed out,
there are key differences
between the Bolton case and the
indictments of James Comey and Lisha James.
As Laura just mentioned,
this indictment is longer.
It was brought by experienced prosecutors,
but here,
too,
President Trump has long railed
against John Bolton,
accusing him of criminal activity,
even calling some of his actions
treasonous.
And remember,
President Trump campaigned on a promise of retribution.
So looking forward, what can we expect?
Look, there are questions about who, if anyone,
could be next just this week,
flanked by his FBI director and attorney general,
the president calling again for his longtime political foe,
Adam Schiff,
to be indicted.
Senator Schiff has consistently said
he has never engaged in any wrongdoing.
Chanel and Willie.
So,
Kristen,
let's turn back to Ukraine for a moment.
President Trump welcoming President Zelensky
to the White House for that meeting today,
but it comes a day after President Trump
announced another meeting with Vladimir Putin.
So what is the administration's strategy here for that war?
Well,
look,
they want to bring this war to an end.
Also,
a key campaign promise for President Trump.
We know today President Zelensky's key focus is
going to try to get assurances from the president
that Ukraine will get those long-range Tomahawk
missiles that would allow Ukraine to strike deep
into Russia.
Ukraine believes that would have a significant
impact on its ability to fight the war.
But look,
there's widespread skepticism that President Putin,
who Mr. Trump did speak with on
Thursday, is actually interested in peace.
One Ukrainian aide telling me Putin is only
interested in diplomacy under the
threat of a gun or a Tomahawk missile.
Still, the Middle East
ceasefire brokered by Mr. Trump does
add some urgency to this entire process.
Willie and Chanel.
All right, a busy time.
Thank you, Kristen.
And a quick programming note,
Ukraine's president,
Zelensky, will be among
Kristen's exclusive guests this Sunday on Meet the Press.
Turning now to the urgent rescues
still underway in Alaska this morning,
where a devastating storm has wiped out entire
communities in remote areas along the state's coastline.
Military planes now being used to evacuate residents there.
And officials calling it one of the most
significant airlift operations in Alaska's history.
NBC's Liz Kreutz joins us now with details.
Liz, good morning.
Hi, Willie.
Good morning to you.
Alaska's governor is now asking the White House to
declare what's happening there a major disaster.
Officials warn that desperately needed
relief efforts could take months.
The Red Cross says many of those areas that have
been impacted are only accessible by air or sea,
meaning that flights to larger cities are
now critical to getting residents to safety.
In Alaska,
a race to evacuate residents to safety.
Officials calling it one of the largest
airlift operations in the state's history.
It comes after a massive storm devastated several
low-lying communities on the state's west coast
with deadly record flooding.
A lot of mess right here that washed all the way up.
Remnants of a typhoon last weekend leaving miles of destruction,
wiping out critical infrastructure,
including many roads.
The storm even pushing some homes off of their foundations.
It has been a disaster of major
proportions and we're moving into winter.
The village of Kipnook overwhelmed with water levels
more than six feet above the highest normal tide line.
It was just so fast.
The water came up and my window broke.
State police reporting at least one
woman died and two others are missing.
She was the kindest person.
She opened her doors to people.
More than 2,000 displaced residents overwhelming
makeshift shelters in the remote communities,
forcing the urgent evacuations.
It started coming into the floor.
The water was scary.
The National Guard airlifting hundreds first
to Bethel and then to Anchorage 500 miles away from their villages.
Entire families and even pets
packing into military planes.
Some evacuees now staying in an emergency shelter at the Alaska
airline center.
This is traumatic.
Folks are coming in here with just clothes on their back,
but Alaskans are tough people.
This morning.
What's next is unknown for Alaskans who have lost
everything and now have no homes to return to.
We're going to start off scratch first new start a new chapter.
Now it's unclear when many of these residents
are going to be able to return home with winter
approaching.
Officials fear these communities are not
going to have access to the construction
materials that they need to rebuild because those
are also going to need to be flown or shipped in.
Willie very remote areas.
Liz, thanks so much.
We appreciate it.
We have a lot more to get to as we turn now to the
NFL and a big upset on Thursday night football.
The Bengals taking on the Steelers in a battle of two quarterbacks
over the age of 40 and it was Joe Flacco who was traded to
the Bengals just 10 days ago leading his team past Aaron Rodgers.
The game coming down to the final seconds.
Snap good,
hold good, kick good.
The Bengals with the 36 yard field goal with 7 seconds to play.
They hold on to win it 33 to 31. Cincinnati
improving to 3 and 4 on the season.
You love to see it.
We're ready for anyone in their 40s of course.
By the way they both played really well.
Maybe not a fluke.
Let's get more 40 year olds out there.
We say.
It's a chance for us to start first check
of the weather as we head into the weekend.
For that we say good morning to our good friend Dylan.
Hey, Dylan.
Good morning guys.
Feeling like fall out there for a lot of folks in the Northeast and
we have this cold front though that's going to drop temperatures
back through the Midwest.
Also bring some showers and storms.
Not so much today,
but watch what happens as we move into tomorrow,
especially down through
southern Illinois into Missouri into Arkansas.
We will see a line of
potentially severe storms develop large hail damaging winds.
I guess would be
the biggest threats.
These aren't going to be too widespread,
but it's really
the heavier rain that will continue to move eastward.
Then we'll see some of
that heavier rain as we go into Sunday
to especially across the eastern Great
Lakes.
But this area is under an extreme drought,
so this is actually beneficial
rain that we are expecting going into the weekend
we can see as much as 1 to 3 inches of rain,
especially from central Michigan right
down into north central parts of Indiana.
We're also looking for lots of sunshine out West
today temperatures comfortable in the 60's and
70's that's look at the weather across the country
will get your local forecast in the next 30 seconds.
It's a chilly fall morning with that outside of talking just a bit
and we'd like to see all of them and all of you back out
there next week for the big kickoff of our today's fan fest
you can call it a family fan fest.
Music there because you
are our family we're inviting you here we're going to
celebrate on Monday on the show it will be the first of a lot
of special events marking you know everything you love about
this show of course the food is great here Willie your show
you're going to sit down Sunday live Jim gaffigan making space
with hoda all the good things that I read with John some
people like that.
Scan the qr code and join us tickets for
those events we love to have here on Monday was going to make
you a believer eventually movies right meantime we'll start
this half hour with something no one likes those annoying robo
calls and text messages new research shows they're actually
getting worse and be sees Tom Costello joins us with
more on this hey Tom. Hey guys you know I was just
looking through my phone I don't know if you can see
this look at all of the phone numbers I've had to
block these are all spam calls I've received block
block block block this is a huge problem it seems
to be getting worse I don't know about you I simply
don't answer my phone or the text message if
I don't recognize the number experts say a lot of
this is a I driven scammers want us to
answer or text back so they know our
number is real don't do it.
I'm calling in regards to your pre-approval for a
credit card consolidation of up to fifty
five thousand dollars no matter your age
or area code everyone gets them this
message is from the taxpayer support
office you've been marked for IRS
resolution options scam robocalls are
exploding and so our tempers nearly a
third of us get at least one call every
day I literally get about 30 calls a day
that's Nielsen or in Dallas she has to
answer every call because she's a
realtor and it could be a customer you
block them and another call comes in
another concoct is that continuous call
so it's yeah it's unbelievable consumer
watchdog purges spam robocalls are up 20
% to a six-year high 420 million more calls each month I
mean these bad guys they put out millions and millions
and they only need just a teensy tiny percentage of
them to work.
While most people don't answer or hang up,
the average person who is scammed loses nearly
$3,700,
easy money for a scammer who could be overseas.
Perg researchers say fewer than half of phone
companies have installed the required caller
ID or filters to block the calls.
The U.S.
telecom industry tells NBC News it disagrees with the Perg findings.
And it says robocalls have actually been declining.
Phone companies,
it says,
have rolled out blocking and labeling tools for their customers
to successfully trace these malicious scammers
and work with law enforcement to shut them
down.
A Consumer Reports investigation finds one
in 10 Americans has now lost money to a scam,
with 18- to 29-year-olds most targeted in texting scams.
The expert advice,
ignore,
delete,
and report suspect calls and texts.
If it's a number you don't recognize
and you're not expecting a phone call,
don't answer it.
Let it go to voicemail.
And try to keep your cool.
When I say take me off the call list,
I mean take me off the call list.
That man speaks for all of us, I think, Tom.
We're all sitting here saying,
I'm glad it's not just me.
We're all getting these calls constantly.
So is there any way to actually get yourself off these call lists?
So a couple of ideas and tips from the FCC. Contact cell phone companies about blocking
tools on the apps they offer.
And then register on that do not call list.
That should help
block telemarketing calls.
Set a voicemail password on your home phone so a hacker can't
gain access to your voicemails.
But listen,
guys,
above all,
be suspicious,
be skeptical
of any code call or a text.
No,
I'm not planning to play golf with you this weekend.
No, we're
not supposed to have lunch next week.
No, I don't know who you are.
Don't answer.
Don't text back.
I will play golf with you though, Willie.
Okay, well, you want to play with both of them.
I was just about to say.
Carson's the guy you want to play with.
Answer that call.
Tom, thanks so much.
It's funny,
I block those calls and now I feel like my phone won't ring,
but it'll go right to voicemail still.
Right.
Yes, I don't know what works.
Yeah.
And they've become kind of convincing,
haven't they?
The calls or the texts you get,
it could be something you need to respond to.
Yeah,
this is a timely story because my phone's blown up just recently,
I lost a couple weeks too with those.
So good stuff there, guys.
Thanks,
Tom. Alright,
still ahead,
let's cue the music for this one.
We are going to celebrate the life of rock and roll legend,
Kiss Guitars,
Ace Fraley.
What we're learning about his sudden passing as,
of course,
the tributes continue to pour in.
But first,
Stephanie Gask is at a popular pickleball court today with a warning
about a dangerous injury tied to the sport that's on the rise.
Good morning.
I mean,
mountain biking,
downhill skiing,
white water rafting,
these are dangerous sports,
but pickleball, you'd be surprised.
All of the details coming up.
We are back at 739 this morning.
I'm in depth today.
We're taking a closer look at the fastest-growing
sport in America,
pickleball,
and the injury that's now rising along with it.
See, Stephanie Gask has that story.
The cheerful sounds from the local pickleball
court definitely do not make anyone think of
it as an extreme sport.
But a new study suggests the game loved for
its everyone-have-fun vibes can actually cause
serious eye injuries.
My action was a little too slow.
It hit the top of my paddle and just ricocheted into my eye.
I'm a little worried about a possible detached retina.
The injuries have become so common,
they're inspiring memes on TikTok.
Pickleball in a helmet may be a joke,
but getting hit by a ball at close range is no
laughing matter.
According to a new study,
pickleball eye injuries can include
retinal detachments and fractures,
even vision loss.
And serious incidents appear to be rising.
In 2024,
pickleball-related eye injuries resulted
in more than 1,200 emergency room visits,
the study's estimate shows,
three times higher than just a few years ago.
70% of those, players 50 and over.
As we get older,
your reaction speed,
your coordination go down as well,
and compounding those issues can make it that
you're gonna get hit more likely by the ball.
With the backing of celebrity investors and famous players,
including tennis legend Andre Agassi,
pickleball's popularity has been skyrocketing.
New numbers show the sport has grown more than 223%
in the past three years,
with increased participation in every age group.
Our own Today Show team has even taken a swing at it.
That was a good one.
The rise in injuries might just be due to more people playing,
the study's authors say,
but eye protection should be emphasized,
like in racquetball or squash.
Sunglasses or
sunglass-type glasses might be enough
if they're impact resistant,
but they have to be impact resistant,
and if not, you definitely wanna wear goggles
that are made specifically for racquet sports.
That was NBC's Stephanie Gask reporting.
Do you wear goggles for?
No, I don't even play the sport, but.
How about you pick a ball for a quick second?
I did for our piece, but that was it, yeah.
I play occasionally, let's just say most of us
are not playing at the speed that some of those videos
we saw where you're gonna get Andre Agassi
ripping a forehand at your face.
I put the whole point with that.
You gotta stay out of the kitchen,
that's the thing, you're too close.
That's the front part.
You gotta play with the two.
Yes, yeah.
I'm a heavy dinker.
I know that's the only joke on the pickleball.
Take it easy out there, guys.
Dinking.
Dinking in the kitchen, yeah, same thing.
All right,
it's time for another check of the weather.
Dylan, what are you looking at?
Glad I learned a few new terms for pickleball
for when I ever play.
We do have very chilly temperatures out there
for a lot of folks in the Northeast.
Frost advisories, freeze warnings.
Again,
this mostly affects the plants and the growing season,
but as you step outside, it's pretty chilly.
Lake Placid, 21 degrees to start off the day.
Buffalo's at 34, Scranton's at 34.
Even across Long Island,
we're in the mid to upper 40s,
down through Elkins,
West Virginia,
we're at 29 degrees.
So the chill is on,
and we also,
as I mentioned earlier,
have these drought conditions across a lot of areas
in the country,
especially up into the Northeast,
where we even have some extreme drought.
So even though we are going to see some rain late on Sunday,
it's nothing too severe,
but it will certainly help a bit
with the drought conditions to really get any rain.
But 34% of the Northeast is in severe drought right now.
We haven't had a lot of rain recently.
We also have this cold front that's going to move
through the Midwest today.
Some isolated late day storms are possible out West.
It's beautiful,
lots of sunshine,
temperatures cooler across the Rockies in the 50s,
but we're looking at 70s for the West Coast.
That's the weather across the country.
Now here's a peek out your window.
And that's your latest forecast.
All right,
guys,
you're in for a good one,
Dilly Dilly.
Let's get to our pop star sneak peek.
PSSP, we like to call it.
Google has revealed the top 10 trending Halloween costumes of 2025.
And there's one particular pop culture craze
that is absolutely dominating the list.
Have any guesses as to what that could be?
Here's a clue.
We're going up, up, up, it's our moment.
You know together we're going.
Gonna be, gonna be going in.
Chanel, you're not wrong with your guess.
We'll get to that in a second.
This is,
yeah,
of course,
six of the top 10 costumes are from Netflix's Smash It.
K-pop Demon Hunters.
We'll take a look at the full list.
From Demon Hunters,
you have all these,
you can be any of these people.
Rumi or Zoe or Mira or one of the
baby Sasha boys or whatever that is.
Also, Minecraft.
Let's just move on to Chicken Jockey.
Chanel, there's your Laboo Boo.
There might even be a few Lafoo Foos out there.
Count the teeth.
Derpy from,
that's also from the Demon Hunters deal.
Elphaba, we know Elphaba.
In the top 10 spots of the Halloween costumes according to Google,
the Lorax is there.
Yes,
we'd like to apologize
to homemade ghost firefighter.
All the original costumes that we wear.
I was proud of my daughter.
They're all getting together.
She's a genie in a bottle.
Like, so she ordered a little
genie thing.
And go with some classics.
We've got Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
Another classic.
Yes.
We're gonna have much more pop star in our next half hour,
but first,
something very special just happened out on
our plaza,
so we've decided to make it our morning boot.
Trust me, you don't want to miss this.
It's coming up right after this.
That's a good idea.
Alright guys, this is very exciting.
We're back with an extremely rare breaking news boost.
We just had a proposal out on our plaza.
And we had a real one.
You're looking at the moment as it happened.
The happy couple,
so of course,
we ran out and asked their names.
Rachel and Luke, they're from Chicago.
They met 10 years ago in college.
She thought they were.
She said yes,
I think she thought they
were in town to visit friends,
but apparently Luke had other
ideas.
So we ran outside.
We gave him a mic.
Can we talk to
him?
All this is exciting.
Yeah, right.
Did you did you got it yet?
So Luke, can we get a little backstory?
How did this come
about?
Well, Rachel is the world's biggest fan of
the Today show.
This has been this trip has been planned for
weeks,
but I had a friend help with some planning with some
signs.
Wow, Rachel, you watch the show a lot.
Obviously, you
know we come out at 830. Why didn't you wait for us?
I know
Carson.
I'm waiting for you.
I need a picture.
You know Carson can do weddings.
Want to
do an impromptu?
That's true.
I am ordained in the state of
Oklahoma for Blake Shelton.
I could legally do it there,
but congratulations.
Where's the
honeymoon?
Who knows?
Was our camera just in happen to be rolling?
yeah,
was our camera just in happen to be rolling had you guys from
your van point what it looked like.
I had to give it some time there was a sign.
There was this sign
help for some time I got some help from the crowd.
The camera
crew then got on camera.
Good job.
And that's out so well,
congratulations for that to say
hi to you all just a few minutes.
Really has a nice gift for you guys.
All right congrats guys
guys that's cool.
I love when the real I was like when I
watched TV other set they seem set up but that's something
happening out the window.
There was a commotion and rice swans
in real time.
Still had we're going to dive into music Friday
we've got that coming up on pop star including some very
personal news that was hidden in Charlie poops latest music
video but we'll take you to the next stop on our Friday morning
lights tour a remarkable high school in Maryland where the
football team is led by a very special.
First local news.
It is 8 o'clock on today coming up high stakes president Trump
said to host Ukraine's leader at the White House just one day
after a surprise phone call with Russia's Vladimir Putin
Trump now saying the second summit with
him is in the works we want to get peace
we want to stop the killing this morning,
the new hope bolstered by the ceasefire
deal in the Middle East that an end to
Russia's war could also be within reach.
A live report from the White House.
Then remembering a spray lead.
We're looking
back at the life and legacy of the kids lead guitarist
who's makeup and music changed rock and
roll the tributes pouring in this morning.
And life and longevity a story all
women need to hear women who undergo
menopause later tend to live longer and we
think if we can extend this ovarian function,
they'll be healthier.
The surprising new keys to living longer from
2 female innovators working to change
the way we think about health and aging.
All that plus all the hits on new music Friday.
I'm a garden heads back to the kitchen
who would like that and we're catching up
with the cast of nobody wants this.
They've made the choice to be together
but you know now what how they going
to do it ahead of the new season.
Everyone
is asking for today Friday October 17th, 2025.
It's what it's what.
My favorite part of the show welcome back to today,
thank
you for joining us on this Friday morning.
Yeah, we'll
unite today in for Savannah and Craig it's been a busy morning
already on that Plaza.
So who knows what's going to happen.
This out there today.
Well,
we have a busy our head for you and big stars
coming your way all next week about this list,
Adam Brody Ethan Hawke Brie
Larson Kristen Bell Jacob
Lordy Ben Stiller and yes,
John Bon Jovi we're sitting down with all of
them next week on today looking forward to it
but right now let's get to your news at 8. We
begin with the latest on the push for peace
between Ukraine and Russia president Trump hosting
president Zelensky at the White House
today just one day after announcing a new
summit with Vladimir Putin and he sees
Peter Alexander is in Washington with
the very latest Peter good morning.
So now good morning just days after
celebrating that ceasefire between Israel
and Hamas president Trump is now turning
his attention to the Russia Ukraine war
president Zelensky is you know that
arrives here this afternoon is expected
to push for American made Tomahawk
missiles that can strike deep inside
Russia in hopes of pressuring Vladimir Putin
to agree to direct negotiations with him nice
to the truck to pull through as we're having this
conversation earlier this week president Trump said
Ukraine wants to go on offense but yesterday he
was non-committal what he says today I think is
going to be telling for where things could go from
here Russia is warned transferring Tomahawks to
Ukraine would mark a dangerous escalation of
tensions between Russia and the US and as for
that next summit after a long surprise call with Putin yesterday
president Trump announced that they will meet in Budapest
Hungary Russia says it could happen in the next few weeks their
last meeting is you remember in Alaska produced no major progress
and Russia has only accelerated its attacks against Ukraine
in the month since Chanel all right Peter thank you president
Trump yesterday announced two new efforts aimed at making in vitro
fertilization more affordable the White House said this truck
a deal with two specialty pharmacies and a drug manufacturer
to lower the cost of a commonly prescribed
fertility drug the administration also
plans on issuing guidance encouraging
employers to offer fertility benefits
directly to their employees which would
work similarly to vision or dental
coverage the guidance does not mandate
that employers participate also this
morning we are remembering an American
original ace Fraley the lead guitarist
of the band kiss passed away yesterday
the legendary rocker was 74 years old
Carson has a look back at his life Carson
yeah she'll thanks Fraley was one of course
the founding members of kiss in its 70s
heyday and he returned during a massive
reunion tour in the 90s the band's bold
makeup and unique musical style inspiring
an entire generation of artists
a rock star attitude bombastic guitar playing
and the distinct black and white stage
makeup ace Fraley tore up the stage
alongside his bandmates of the iconic
band kiss Fraley's family announcing the
guitarist death on Thursday writing we're
completely devastated and heartbroken
Fraley joined Paul Stanley Gene Simmons
and Peter Chris to form kiss in New York
City back in 1973 Fraley better known
as space ace or spaceman by devoted kiss
fans was a Bronx native and considered
one of the greatest metal guitarists of
all time putting his unmistakable sound
on kiss hits and finding massive success
with his hit single New York Groove from his 1978 solo album
Fraley eventually leaving the band in
1982 explaining on today I got into the
music business because I was having a
great time when it wasn't fun anymore I
had to leave he rejoined kiss in 1996
and gave an iconic performance at the
closing ceremony of the Winter Olympics in Salt Lake
City while his family did
not release a cause of death last month
the guitarist fell in his studio and was
taken to the hospital according to his
now deleted social media post on September
25th as a result he canceled the
remainder of his tour dates for the year
this morning fans leaving flowers on his
Walk of Fame star in Los Angeles while
tributes are pouring in with former
bandmates Gene Simmons and Paul Stanley
paying tribute writing we are devastated
by the passing of ace Fraley he was an
essential and irreplaceable rock soldier
The original for members of Kiss of course were ducked in the
Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2014 Fraley never stopped making
music in fact last year released a solo album 10,000 volts which
topped billboards hard music and rock albums chart of course
there's tributes pouring in from all sorts of as you can imagine
every current rock star from a tallica Dave Grohl Billy Corgan
rock and roll bands they are there's so many great songs and
he's such a great guitar players at the core that to
yeah Larry Carson thanks let's turn a baseball now the L.A.
Dodgers just one win away from a return trip to the World
Series the Dodgers had only 5 hits last night but it was
enough to beat the Milwaukee Brewers in game 3 of the NLCS
3 to 1 the Dodgers now can close out that series and go
to the World Series tonight in L.A.
over the American League
the Toronto Blue Jays even things up in the LCS said 2 games
a piece Vladimir Guerrero junior home run for the second
straight night blue just blow out the Mariners 8 to 2 all
evened up now with game 5 tonight.
And that is the news
now
let's go back over to Carson for a look ahead to pop
start.
I'm here now guys coming up we are learning about a
wicked good surprise that is apparently waiting for fans in
that new movie will have that in a ton more come up your pops
are in a bitch now all right the first Maria Shriver joins us with
a story that all women need to see on the part of the body that could
hold the key to living longer and healthier we'll be right back.
Welcome back at 8.11 this morning in your health is
surprising new keys to longevity for women our friend and
striver sat down with two innovators who are rewriting
Good morning.
Good morning
guys.
Well women typically live longer than men.
We all know that but that doesn't mean that they live better.
In older age women
are more likely to suffer from a whole host of debilitating diseases.
Now you're about to meet two women who are trying to
change that in some very unexpected ways.
In the race to live longer and better these
innovators are breaking the mold focusing
on surprising new areas of a woman's body.
We
can't have a discussion of health span
without including a discussion of our ovaries.
That's
right the ovaries.
Well they're typically associated with fertility.
Francesca Duncan
a top researcher at Northwestern says the ovaries are
also critical to a woman's longevity producing
estrogen and other hormones essential to healthy living.
Estrogen is really important for cardiovascular
health bone health immune health cognitive health.
And so what happens with age is that there is a decline
in the number of eggs that are in the ovary and as
such there's less hormones that are being produced.
Now Duncan and her team are researching how to
slow down ovarian aging in mice and extend hormone
production into later age by delaying menopause.
Women who undergo menopause later tend to live longer and we
think if we can extend this ovarian function they'll be healthier.
Somebody might hear that and say are you suggesting
then that women should be able to have babies
in their 50s and 60s that they can get pregnant.
So that is not our goal.
She hopes in the next decade researchers will
develop a pill that extends hormone production
just long enough to produce longevity benefits.
Duncan says while current hormone therapy during menopause can help
with aging younger women should also focus on their ovarian health.
I have two 30 something year old daughters and they're going to ask
me what can I do right now in my 30s so that my ovaries don't age.
I think lifestyle interventions are
important and something that we can control.
Research shows ovarian
function can be impacted by being
overweight smoking and drinking alcohol.
But when it comes to
longevity experts say there's another body part
many women ignore altogether their muscles.
If we
really want to age well we have to start focusing on skeletal muscle.
Dr. Gabrielle Lyon is a
bestselling author and founder of the
Institute for Muscle Centric Medicine.
She says building muscle can lower the risk of diabetes
heart disease and Alzheimer's while dramatically
improving bone strength and mobility in older age.
Most women think about like I want to be thin.
So women have been eating salads or eating nothing at all.
They've been doing cardio.
Are you advocating that that's been the wrong approach.
Yes it is actually.
When you have healthy muscle you're able to
store carbohydrates
get glucose out of the bloodstream which is toxic
at high levels to both the brain and the body.
In her forever strong playbook out early next year Lyon
offers strength training programs for women of all abilities.
The simple act of putting a weight vest on and going for a walk
even if your body composition is not changing the health and
quality of your muscle tissue is and it is changing immediately.
She says just 20 minutes of
intense resistance training three days a week combined with a balanced
diet high in lean protein can supercharge your health at any age.
There is data in 80 to 90 year olds that
when they start this they will see changes.
It's never too late to get strong ever.
But Dr. Lyon says strength training has similar longevity
benefits in men and the younger you start the better the results.
She herself has two young kids and
they already work out with weights.
Now as far as G.L.P.
drugs are concerned Dr. Lyon says if you are taking one it's
really important to eat enough protein and to have a good
strength training program so that your muscles are not neglected.
So you guys never too late to get going on that great thanks
Maria are too late for anything that's right that's right.
Thanks Maria.
All right Mister daily a look at pops all right
guys let's get to it will start today,
it's been a while since
we've had any music Friday will do that they will kick it off
with Charlie
Puth yesterday the chart topper dropped a music
video for his new song changes with his wife,
Brooke and the
couple snuck in a pretty big announcement take a look.
There is there.
Expecting baby number one congratulations to
those guys.
We caught that speaking of a couple of
chemistry about Thomas retinile horn these 2 music superstars
just teamed up for a new version of Rett song old tricks
here's a listen to that.
You got to hear Nile talk about his love
of country music and it seems like a far
disconnect because of one direction in
this history there but Irish traditional
music that he loves so much grow with this very much in the
storytelling Rome's country so he actually is a good accent.
Yeah,
no one is saying so there's not everybody's going
country,
I know everybody next up wicked for good director
John M Chu just used a mystery actor is set to voice this
character in wicked next chapter.
I have any courage at all.
I even scare myself.
Look at the cycles of the my eyes haven't slept in weeks.
Why is playing the cowardly line in wicked for good will
according to true he booked some major Hollywood star by
DMing them on instagram and while he will not reveal that
celebrity as he did tell deadline man wait until the red
carpet when the actor who gave us the cowardly lions voice
steps foot on it will be wild what a tea crazy to us who is
market calendar so the big reveal wicked for good from our
sister company universal pictures hits theaters.
November
21st, I guess I mean no idea yeah there.
Next up I know garden this weekend,
her food network
series be my guest returns for a new season with Tina Fey
joining the culinary icon for the premiere and we have a pop
start exclusive sneak peek.
Yeah,
you're had to eat anything really strange on the
set I've eaten entire pizzas really yeah,
it was just written
that I shot going to pizza.
I didn't have a plan.
My instincts
kicked in and I threw open the box folded the pizza into
quarters and I went from the middle out.
I was very good at
it.
I know what I promise you want to see a fan or world
little season premiere of be my guest of the Ina Garten debuts
this Sunday over on the food network.
Finally Michael J.
Fox,
I'm not sure how we scored this exclusive announcement that
we have here but that's because it will be the center of your
conversation for really is a Sunday sit down this weekend,
the Hollywood a list are opening up about being called into
the family ties creators office just 23 years old and getting
offered back to the future.
But what I want to do is he has a lot of things said that
this movie you do is if you want to do it will make it work.
I think that all of them.
That's a great and that the woman started.
I've seen a couple interviews with him what he seems to be
doing great.
He's doing great he's he's doing really well he
looks great.
He's so he's such a light to him and such a warmth
and aside from the activism that he's done on behalf of
Parkinson's patients,
he's still talking about his career
in such a joyful way it's got this book out marking 40 years
of back to the future.
He was already starring on family ties
and family ties that you can go do this movie.
But you're going
to shoot all day family time.
Yes, and he said don't
complain about it.
Yeah, this about that movie.
Wow get in a
car go to the other side of la and shoot back to future all
night.
Sleep for like weeks and weeks and weeks, but it
certainly paid off for that is a yeah,
that was my future
reminder tune in in case you don't know will just tune into
this great interview.
Sunday this Sunday right on this net
on NBC. Yes, Sir, I'll be there.
Good.
All right, let's turn
from pop star to Friday morning.
We love highlighting high
school football teams across the country this morning we got
a good one for you taking you to Forest Heights,
Maryland,
home of the oxen Hill Clippers.
We're ricketts and it is Washington is there for us
along with Jeffries good morning guys.
My gosh good morning,
you all New York,
this is what I live
for my goodness Friday morning life.
Auxen Hill in Maryland right now they've got a game tonight,
they're 5 in one they're taking on flowers high school at 6.30
we've got our principal here.
We've got alumni here look at that alumni from the 80's and 90's and
of course we've got the man of the hour coach Jeffries Jeffries I
got to talk to you a little bit now listen you guys have a 100 years
of clipper pride what does it mean tonight to play under the lights.
It's a big deal for us to celebrate not centennial school this year.
We got a good team with five and one right now.
We're looking to move in advance to the playoffs.
Now,
a hundred year legacy for this school,
that is insane.
What does this school and this team mean to this community?
This school means a whole lot to the community.
We have a lot of hard work.
There's the harbors down the street.
We have a science tech program
that produces a lot of high academic kids
and great kids, great place to work,
great place to play football.
That's awesome.
Now, hey, listen, you are a local man.
He went to Dunbar High School and you taught there for a little bit,
coached there for a little bit.
Now you're back here.
This is your 15th season here.
And you, if you win tonight, get that win.
Two hundred wins, correct?
That's correct.
What's it going to take to secure that win tonight?
It's going to take these guys to do what they normally do,
play hard,
work hard,
play fast and just play together as a team.
And we'll be fine.
Yeah.
Are you guys ready to play?
We've got the quarterback,
who's a junior right here.
He's ready to play.
All these guys are ready to play.
Interviewed you early.
You ready to play?
Now, listen, we've got a lot of pride here.
In fact, we had some sparklers earlier.
I want to show you all,
but they've been running them all morning
because of the pride that they have here.
So unfortunately,
they're out,
but we got enough pride,
right?
Yeah.
And we've got the X Factor dance team.
So I want to show you what they've got going on as well.
X Factor, let's go ahead and take it away, guys.
I love it.
Clippers.
Getting busy tonight.
I'm taking them in the over.
Yeah.
And our thanks to Lauren there,
all of our friends helping us
out at NBC4 Washington.
Did such a great job this morning.
That looked awesome.
The whole time,
Willie was trying to fit this hat in.
It's so small.
Willie and I have a regular hat.
That's a fair trade.
Fair trade.
Go guys.
Go Clippers.
Yes.
Coming up,
a closer look at Taylor Swift's stunning
engagement ring from the woman who made it,
designer Kendrick
Lubeck,
who calls Taylor amazing or calls her Taylor
calls her amazing.
She's here to see you.
I mean, I think it's a mutual love.
Your local moves.
And we've got Sunday night football.
You know,
if Al was here,
he'd say it's the Falcons.
Headed to San Francisco to take on the 49ers.
Looks beautiful in Santa Clara, clear and
mild 70 degrees,
a beautiful night for football night in
America.
Chanel.
All right.
Thank you, Dylan.
We are so excited to introduce
you to our next guest jewelry designer Kendrick Lubeck.
She's a goldsmith,
hand engraver and vintage jewelry
collector.
And you might recognize her name because of
the very special piece she created for a certain music
star.
Take a look.
I just caught a glimpse of the ring.
Oh, yeah.
You want to see?
Yes, we do.
So am I right in saying that Travis designed that ring?
He did.
He designed it with this amazing this amazing jeweler.
Kendrick Lubeck is her name,
and she does all of her gold engraving by hand.
And I had shown him a video of like
I just thought her stuff was so cool.
So I had shown him a video like a year and a half ago.
And he was just paying attention to everything.
It turns out because when I saw the ring,
I was like,
I know who made that.
How cool is that?
And now we're here with the woman who made that ring.
Kendrick, good morning to you.
Hi, Kendrick.
Hi, it's so nice to be here.
I told you I went in a deep dive on your Instagram last night.
So it must feel pretty cool to hear Taylor sing your praises.
Oh, my gosh.
Yes.
And the fact that she recognized my work,
that is such an incredible honor.
She said, I know who made that.
I,
when I heard her say that,
I thought that was the most exciting thing.
I love hearing that Trav was listening a year and a half ago.
He stored that away somewhere in case that day came.
What has it been like since she's gone public and
talked about you as the designer of this beautiful ring?
What's it been like for you personally and for business?
For me personally, it's just
like this is something that I think
you only dream of happening to you.
And so it's incredibly surreal.
Like I have a pinch me moment every day.
But also it's just such an honor.
Like I feel so honored.
Well, I was reading about you.
I know you've worked incredibly hard to get here.
This didn't happen overnight.
So when did you get into hand-graving rings and the
intricacy that you do?
Right.
Yeah.
So I think that was 2021 is when I took my first engraving course.
And I was bit immediately.
I was totally hooked.
I stayed way after hours at my dad's store.
And I was coming in on weekends and I was just obsessed with it.
So you kind of grew up around it.
You mentioned your dad's store.
From a young age,
you were very interested in this business.
Well,
so actually the fact that I joined the business was a
surprise.
Yeah.
So even though I did grow,
like there are,
I have a baby picture of me and my dad's chair in front of his
Ben. But it was,
you know,
I have a degree in psychology.
So it was a really,
it was a surprise that I joined.
But it was like
it was like the most natural thing in the world.
So I love
that Taylor Swift is a fan.
And so everybody is now looking
at your Instagram page.
I heard everything's like sold out.
So popular,
but you can show us some of the popular things
that people are talking about.
So the first one, obviously
hand engraving.
Can you show us some examples?
Yeah.
So this is
a great example of hand engraving.
See if we can get the
camera there.
Which one?
See if it all pops out.
Oh, wait,
look.
Oh, oh, perfect.
There we go.
Yes. So this is the Nixie
pendant.
It looks,
it reflects back like water,
like sunlight on water.
That's cool.
Yeah.
And that's hand work you've done all that.
That's one of your signatures, right?
Yes. Okay.
Let's talk about antique stones.
What are we talking about here?
Yes. So this is an excellent example of an antique stone.
Okay.
This one.
Yeah.
This is an old mine cut diamond.
Yes. And it just,
you see how it has these big broad facets,
whereas a modern cut.
That is bling.
Yeah.
The modern cuts are like more like a disco ball.
They, they're super sparkly.
Whereas the old cuts are just like a little bit more.
The flashes are broader.
It's like creates this kind of romantic subtlety.
So. And I've noticed you talk a lot about colored stones too,
or you have some of those.
Yes. I love colored stones.
What are we looking at here?
This is a stunning blue sapphire.
And that one is actually from Sri Lanka.
This one is Montana.
That's beautiful.
And then platinum is another area you like working in,
right?
Well, so I expect platinum to be on the rise,
but I, I work predominantly in gold.
I expect platinum to be on the rise for two reasons.
The first reason is the cost of gold is soaring.
The second reason is that gold has been in like really,
really,
really popular for about say five years.
So that pendulum does kind of start to swing back into the,
another direction.
So I don't think gold is going anywhere.
I don't think it's going out,
but I expect platinum to be on the rise.
One last question.
Do you design Superbowl rings?
I would say, yeah.
I was just about to say,
I'm like,
can you say yes?
How amazing would that be?
The patience of us take to,
to sit there and do that.
It doesn't feel like I have to have patience for it.
What?
Are you kidding?
No, it doesn't.
I, it's so Zen.
It is such a meditative experience for me to start engraving.
It's amazing.
It was only four years ago.
You take an engraving class and here you are now.
I couldn't have told you,
like I had no idea that I would,
couldn't have.
Well, congratulations.
You're really good at it.
Your household name now.
Thank you, Kindred.
Thanks Kindred.
Good to meet you.
Coming up next, we'll take you behind the scenes
of one of TV's hottest shows.
Nobody wants this.
Jacob Soboroff's visit to that set
and what the stars are revealing now about season two.
But first this is today on NBC.
Nobody wants this became a breakout hit
when it debuted just over a year ago.
And now the countdown is on for season two guys.
Just a few days ago.
Of course,
fans can't wait to find out what's to come.
And this morning we're getting a
little peek from the stars of the show.
Our good friend,
NBC's Jacob Soboroff caught up with the cast as they wrapped
filming and even got to join them on the set.
Part of being in a relationship is dealing with these issues.
And we will feel like we've been saying that a lot.
The show is called
Nobody Wants This,
but that couldn't be further from the truth.
When there's this much engagement around it makes you proud,
but also
happy that people maybe wanted to see a love story.
The Netflix mega hit returns for a second
season next week with Kristen Bell and Adam
Brody reprising their roles as agnostic
podcaster Joanne and young rabbi Noah,
an unlikely couple that viewers are rooting for.
You're converting to Judaism.
No,
we're going to do the whole like interfaith thing.
Well,
You get to see the fun struggles layered in with
comedy and then you get to see a really kind of like
Satisfying outcome there's only room for
one perfect person in this relationship
Show was based on writer creator Aaron Foster's life her story
Resonating with audiences Aaron calls the show justice
for healthy relationships being the most romantic
Mmm,
you like that.
I love that.
I like that too.
Yeah being supported being as selfless as you
can for a partner is a very romantic thing
What is it about the characters?
Do you think
that that has resonated with so many people?
It's really about two people
Coming to a relationship in their late
30s when you've already fully formed your worldviews
I just tried to think small and specific and
I think that that maybe is why it connects
Jenny Connor of girls fame has gone
from fan to co-showrunner for season 2
These characters feel very very real and very very
flawed in a lot of ways and I think people are like
Oh, those are real people
Justine loop Timothy Simons and Jackie tone all returned.
Okay.
Wow, clearly I struck a nerve
Like I always assumed it would be popular because it is
a show in which Kristen Bell and Adam Brody will kiss
So like people are gonna go.
Yeah.
Hell yeah, like that watch that.
Yeah, like I watch that
The most romantic thing that anyone's
ever done on planet earth you go
I think that
we're like seeing
Emotionally evolved human beings going through like the
classic rom-com in a way that we don't normally get to see that
We love it so much and so does everyone
it's like a once a career feeling
They'll be joined by some familiar faces like guest
star Seth Rogen and Brody's wife Leighton Meester
It's fun to watch her work it's fun to carpool too as for what
to expect this season they've made the choice to be together but
You know now what how they gonna do it?
How they gonna do that?
The cast remained tight-lipped about plot lines
But actress Jackie Tann snuck us on set for
a pivotal scene shot in the middle of LA
This feels it this could be a barista.
This could be a wedding could be a miss could be a wedding could be
any sort of party that our heart is
Involved in in between takes the actor snapped selfies
and even found time for some hobbies this woman miss
As for what happened when the camera started
rolling you'll have to wait for that.
Thank you so much for coming today show
This is nobody wants this mission guys.
We have the best time with you today.
I have to go
today
See you Jackie
Such a good show I got to play golf
with Tim Simons and I tried to be cool
But I really wanted to just fangirl show
he's in but it's really it's a good watch
It's what I'll say.
I love that show.
We should tell you by the way Adam and Kristen
Yeah,
we'll be here live in studio next week and season two
of nobody wants this is out on Netflix on October 23rd
Carson well guys,
it's a party at the Daily House Lord knows
what's happening there because we're here
So coming up today food loves football series in the house.
We got some of our game day favorites
I'm gonna make them for you show you how to do it very easy.
But first is today on NBC
Don't already a whole strombole unbelievable we're back with
today's food loves football the Falcons taken on 49ers as you
can see here Sunday night on the network competition going to
be fierce no competition to studio one a all love here got
my lovely wife,
one of the greatest chefs in manhasset Long
Island.
In the House together we're going to share a couple
game day favorites.
Let's start with the stromboli I don't even
know where this came from but I'm believes are like rolled
pizza.
So you know we do a lot of pizza in our house we do the
fun way to kind of get all those flavors show store-bought pizza
dough and you can make your own but this will keep it nice and
easy.
And then pizza sauce.
I want to say you make our pizza
doughs and you've done it where you do like a 2 day thing where
it sits you also some very fast recipe so this could be made
in like 20 minutes right.
Yes, 100%. You know, it's really
easy with just store-bought pizza dough and you want to
leave a little bit of room on the edges for the rolling
process so that everything doesn't use out.
And then the
one we're going to make is a very you know carnivore lover
meaty stromboli but you can use anything you can swap this with
veggies why would you have meat.
You know you have in your
fridge really works for that.
What was that from bowling.
Best from believe it so.
Well,
Siri is a jam and huge and then has it be yes.
Like it's just perfect good good good so yeah,
we have ham
we've got pepperoni cooked sausage and then I will show
you how you roll it we never know who's going to show up in
our house on the weekend.
So we do like to make this is true
this is what we must make tons of stuff and then it ultimately
gets eaten because we have teenagers what if nobody show
you're going to really have we have a look at us still.
Me rather.
Okay so we roll like this and then you're going to
want to put it down on the side and there's sort of pinch the
edges we're going to brush it with an egg wash is this one
not look like this one because I was because you're talking to
me let's see which one did Siri and which one did that crew
right get that.
Top it with Parmesan some Italian
seasoning and the last thing you want to do is just put a
couple little slicks in it that's what sort of let out the
steam when you cook it and it won't you know love this pop up
too much you know Matt Sheeran he would love this shot.
That's your.
Yeah, that's fan.
This comes over for Sunday Monday.
Yeah, love the time
for like my turn.
Yeah, I don't know where this came from but
we decided to make a Buffalo chicken dip and I want to shout
out London.
I are 11 year-old to come this morning that this
is her jam I'm going to make one this weekend.
I again what with the store bought chicken I do like to smoke a
lot of my meets but I didn't waste the time so this is a rotisserie
chicken I don't use the force actually do like to use my hands
because it helps me ensure that
I can feel what's flesh and what little bones.
So we're going to go ahead and break this all down I love
the dark meat but will mix it all up with the white
me you get a lot of meat off these things will do that and
that's what's over here magically a couple of cheeses
are going to go into this Buffalo dip of course,
your store
and really you could call these a great little melting cheese,
I discovered,
but this is mozzarella and cheddar the
must-haves here we're going to put a healthy amount of those
in there.
I also like to do a little ranch dressing and blue
cheese both in there and people think it's a competition not
they coexist together nicely so we're going to do that and
I just Frank's red hot is going to
make that Buffalo flavor without it being overly spicy.
It's really the Frank's I feel like has the perfect amount
it's not too hot to add some heat to it,
I don't read this is
important.
This is a ranch seasoning salt.
So we're going to put some of that in there and then I've got
some garlic salts and some regular salt and pepper going to
do that we're going to mix all this yummy this together and
then we're going to put a call for like one of the cream cheese
I double the cream cheese.
Wow that is the pro tip of this
whole thing whatever recipe use double the cream cheese that
bowl.
I mean no.
Together in there please tell me that this is like an episode
of I love Lucy.
I'm Lucy in the marriage.
He washes his hands and just goes like this.
I will.
This is a list.
Well, here's the key about the see
if you throw it in the skillet person you're making.
You put in
the oven and we put it out a Jackson my son decided to take
some toast and do some real fire on the toast which makes a
great dip almost like a grilled cheese.
Yeah, or you can put
out the tortilla chips.
But as people come for the the game
this weekend.
When this sits like a like a so dip coagulate so quickly this
you put pop back in the oven for like 5 minutes with little
cheese and reconfigure it's like you just made a new one every
time you do that.
You're.
Magic trick.
I love.
It's like a.
It's so good.
Better than it looks even folks are great to see this.
Don't.
You talk to the Taylor Swift ring person but going to
yeah, keep your way from there.
I'm delicious.
Thank you
Chanel.
Thank you guys the recipes are today dot com slash
food or if you're in the hood stop by the crib.
Falcons
Niners Niners got 19 guys on I are who's going to win this
game.
Niners are favored by less than 3. I like the Falcons
but that's just me 7PM Eastern we're back in a moment.
This is
today on NBC.
We're still talking about yeah,
I think this in the struggle
like a buffalo.
Coming up in the 3rd hour, the best books to
enjoy this fall whether you're in the mood for something cozy
or scared and Jen is with Matt Rogers,
but first local news
and weather about get in there.
The writers.
Hey thanks for watching don't forget you can catch the today
morning on NBC or take today when you're on the go.
follow the today podcast on Apple podcast Spotify or
wherever you listen.